<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Causal ML with DoubleML</title>
    <link>https://doubleml.github.io/tutorial/stable/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Causal ML with DoubleML</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://doubleml.github.io/tutorial/stable/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Welcome UseR!2022</title>
      <link>https://doubleml.github.io/tutorial/stable/2022/06/15/welcome-user-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://doubleml.github.io/tutorial/stable/2022/06/15/welcome-user-2022/</guid>
      <description>Causal Machine Learning with DoubleML Welcome to the UseR!2022 tutorial &amp;ldquo;Causal machine learning with DoubleML&amp;rdquo; taking place virtually on June 20, 2022 from 4:00 to 7:30am CDT.
On this website you&amp;rsquo;ll find all materials that are used during the tutorial. We will share the materials with participants here just before the tutorial starts.
The tutorial is split into four parts:
Introduction to Double Machine Learning Slides, Speaker notes Shiny app Key Ingredients of Double Machine Learning Introduction to the DoubleML Package for R Slides, Speaker notes Demand Elasticity Notebook] (.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://doubleml.github.io/tutorial/stable/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://doubleml.github.io/tutorial/stable/about/</guid>
      <description>DoubleML - Double Machine Learning in R The R package DoubleML provides an implementation of the double / debiased machine learning framework of Chernozhukov et al. (2018). It is built on top of mlr3 and the mlr3 ecosystem (Lang et al., 2019).
Note that the R package was developed together with a python twin based on scikit-learn. The python package is also available on GitHub and PyPI version.
Documentation and maintenance User guide: https://docs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DoubleML Tutorial- Team</title>
      <link>https://doubleml.github.io/tutorial/stable/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://doubleml.github.io/tutorial/stable/team/</guid>
      <description>Philipp Bach Philipp Bach is a postdoctoral researcher in statistics at the University of Hamburg, Germany. His research focuses on implementing and applying methods for causal machine learning. He is a developer and contributor to the R packages DoubleML and hdm. He enjoys being part of the R community and is looking forward to get to know the tutorial participants at useR!2022. Visit Philipp&amp;rsquo;s accounts on twitter @PhilippBach_HH and GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>https://doubleml.github.io/tutorial/stable/getstarted/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://doubleml.github.io/tutorial/stable/getstarted/</guid>
      <description>InstallationPlease read the following installation instructions and make sure you installed the latest release of DoubleML on your local machine prior to our tutorial.
In case you want to learn more about DoubleML upfront, feel free to read through our user guide.
Install latest release from CRANInstall latest release from CRAN via
install.packages(&amp;quot;DoubleML&amp;quot;)Install development version from GitHubThe DoubleML package for R can be downloaded using the command (previous installation of the remotes package is required).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
